TASHA TRAN

701.781.5058 trn.tasha@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/tasha-tran

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Experienced Professional with a proven ability to work under strict deadlines, meet and exceed goals, and get results in the banking service environment. Currently working towards a Full Stack Web Development certificate focusing on the following skills:

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery
- MySQL, MongoDB
- Github

EXPERIENCE

USBANK

Risk Compliance Audit Specialist 3 (OCT 2018 - CURRENT)

- Utilizes research skills by using internal systems and internet search tools to support risk-based decisions
- Works cooperatively with internal business lines to obtain and analyze necessary information related to the investigation
- Demonstrates attention to detail by ensuring alerts worked are adjudicated per department's procedures
- Monthly review feedback and metrics show consistently in the top 3 for production

Risk Compliance Audit Specialist 2 (MAR 2018 - OCT 2018)

- Identified and escalated matters requiring attention to the appropriate area
- Utilized analytical and research skills to adjudicate cases
- Assisted with the implementation of internal policies and procedures to ensure compliance with laws and regulations
- Consistently processed alerts with little to no errors

Mortgage Loan Processor (NOV 2016 - DEC 2017)

- Created initial loan estimates for refinances and purchases
- Ensured files were in compliance to meet both State and Federal Regulations
- Communicated with internal staff and brokers to resolve problems and obtain necessary documents
- Successfully learned proprietary software programs to complete duties

Fraud Risk Analyst (AUG 2013 - NOV 2016)

- Analyzed alerted debit card transactions to prevent and minimize financial loss from fraudulent activity.
- Gathered key risk indicators and reported them to management promptly to prevent potential fraud loss on other cards
- Worked with merchants to resolve customer service issues resulted from fraudulent activity
- Awarded "great catches" for detecting non-transparent fraudulent transactions

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Business Administration (BBA), North Dakota State University

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp, University of Minnesota (pending graduation in 03/2020)